https://pipevet.com/privacy-policy/

$0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Vaccines for Cattle
Companion Pet Products (select clinic below)Independence IA Clinic
Chutes
ServicesBovine ServicesCompanion Animal ServicesSwine Services
Vaccines for Cattle
Companion Pet Products (select clinic below)Independence IA Clinic
Chutes
ServicesBovine ServicesCompanion Animal ServicesSwine Services
About UsOur TeamCompany HistoryContact Us
Careers
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
PVS collects and utilizes personal information provided by you when creating an account. The type of information that may be collected includes: name, postal address, phone, email address, account information, and credit card information.
PVS also receives information automatically whenever someone uses our sites. When your web browser accesses our site, we obtain information such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, access times, page visits, and the number of visits.
The personal information we collect from customers is used for a variety of purposes:
To provide and deliver products and services including confirmations, invoices, updates, security alerts, recall notices, and administrative messages.
To respond to your comments and questions.
To send you communications that we see of benefit to you and your business including educational articles, promotions, events, etc.
Maintain and administer your account.
Improve our website and service offerings.
We may share personal information with third parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf for the purposes identified above.
You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Pipestone Veterinary Services’ by following instructions in those emails, or contacting us at customerservice@pipevet.com or 507.825.4211. If you opt-out, we will still send you non-promotional emails regarding your purchases, account, etc.
If your personal information changes, we encourage you to update it on our website.
We take your privacy and personal information very seriously. If you have questions or comments regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at customerservice@pipevet.com or 507.825.4211.
hidden 507.825.4211 (Pipestone, MN Office)
hidden Swine Order: 507.562.PIGS(7447)
© 2018 Pipestone Veterinary Services. All Rights Reserved.
Back to Top
